{
    "subject": "resource/Lucian_Freud",
    "predicate": "property/birthName",
    "object": "Lucian Michael Freud",
    "human_readable": "The birth name of Lucian Freud is Lucian Michael Freud.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.972658634185791,
            "question": "Is 'Lucian'  the last name of Lucian Freud at birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9656561017036438,
            "question": "What is the surname of Lucian Freud at birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9598907232284546,
            "question": "What was Lucian Freud's birth name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9055391550064087,
            "question": "Who is Lucian Michael Freud?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9020012617111206,
            "question": "What is the first name of Lucian Freud at birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8971632122993469,
            "question": "How many names are in Lucian Freud's birth name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8730241656303406,
            "question": "What are the parts of Lucian Freud's full birth name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8022288680076599,
            "question": "What is the middle name of Lucian Freud?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.718083381652832,
            "question": "Does Lucian Freud have a middle name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.653732180595398,
            "question": "Is 'Lucian Michael Freud'  Lucian Freud's full legal name?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The birth name of Lucian Freud is Lucian Michael Freud.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3995_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Lucian Freud have a middle name?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3995_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the middle name of Lucian Freud?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3995_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are the parts of Lucian Freud's full birth name?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3995_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3995_120.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3995_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3995_143.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3995_149.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3995_150.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3995_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3995_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3995_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3995_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3995_72.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have more triples to evaluate!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "After reviewing the context information, I found that:\n\n* There are multiple documents describing the life and background of Lucian Freud, but none of them mention a \"birth name\" or an alternative name to \"Lucian Michael Freud\".\n* Some documents mention his full name as \"Lucian Michael Freud\", while others simply use \"Lucian Freud\". However, there is no information to suggest that he had a different birth name.\n\nGiven this analysis, I would conclude:\n\n{'output': 'no'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide information about Lucian Freud, including his full name as \"Lucian Michael Freud,\" which supports the statement that his birth name is indeed \"Lucian Michael Freud.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The context information shows multiple statements with the same name \"Lucian Michael Freud\", but some of them lack the middle name \"Michael\".",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}